<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (C) 2016 The Android Open Source Project

     Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
     you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
     You may obtain a copy of the License at

          http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

     Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
     distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
     WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
     See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
     limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>

    <string name="virag_etterem_descript">Virág Étterem is Szeged\'s most well know restaurant with
    vast history and high quality foods!</string>

    <string name="halaszcsarda_descript">Halászcsárda creates one of Hugary\'s most well-known dishes
    the so-called <i>halászlé</i>, a soup made of fish. A true delicacy!</string>

    <string name="john_bull_pub_description">The John Bull Pub is a well known, local restaurant
        with a reputation for exciting, creative cooking and a superlative wine list .
        The talented chef and his team provide inventive cooking with intriguing combinations of ingredients
        designed to surprise and thrill with some simpler classics, wonderfully flavoured dishes
        based on fresh, locally sourced, seasonal produce.</string>

    <string name="taj_maha_description">Taste the tantalizing menu and
        authentic Indian atmosphere at the TAJ MAHAL Restaurant. If you want to feel exotic subcontinental
        flavors of Hungary, with an assortment of delectable dishes including exquisite meat dishes
        and splendid vegetarian meals.</string>
    <string name="art_hotel_description">The ARTHotel Szeged is located in downtown Szeged facing
        directly to the Cathedral Square (Dóm tér). Four star rooms, a modern restaurant, well-equipped
        conference rooms and a variety of relaxing spa services make our hotel the trendiest in town
        that has been already recognized by many awards. ART Hotel Szeged is the perfect choice for
        the city breakers, theatre fans, art enthusiasts, water sports lovers and business travellers.</string>

    <string name="tiszavirag_description">The Tiszavirág is a wonderfully renovated historical townhouse
        with an inner court in the centre of Szeged. The hotel houses 12 different sized rooms,
        a bar, restaurant, café, conference room and SPA. It is an ideal place for those who are
        looking for a boutique-style hotel for fine dining, business, relaxation and entertainment.
        Our conference room is a perfect venue for companies to hold meetings, workshops or training
        events.</string>

    <string name="science_description">With the water kettle you will find premium quality coffee and tea stocked
        in your room; the air conditioner in the room can be set individually and there is a USB port
        for charging portable devices in each room. This is all the wonderful comfort you can get in the
        amazing Science Hotel that welcomes all scientists traveling and everyone who just wants to spend
        a lovely time in Szeged!</string>

    <string name="auris_description"> Hotel Auris is the newest business hotel of Szeged, located in
        the heart of the city, near to Dóm square, even so in quiet, peaceful environment.
        Only a few minutes walk from the beautiful banks of river Tisza. Plenty of comfort to do your
        work better and to relax: fre Wi-Fi, comfortable rooms, great coffe and a lovely staff!</string>

    <string name="szegedzoo_description">The zoo with the largest land area in Hungary has been
        receiving visitors since 1989. Although it is located a mere 2.5 km from the city centre
        of Szeged, it lies in a natural environment. The oak forest and Lake Sancer promise a
        pleasant and calming experience by themselves. However, the animal collection offers
        exciting encounters, as visitors can see several true curiosities along with zoo favourites,
        such as lions, giraffes, meerkats, and Asian elephants (the latter from May 2018).
        Besides these, the Zoo is conducting conservation and educational activities that are outstanding in the region.</string>

    <string name="votive_description">The Votive Church was consecrated on 24th October, 1930.
        The cathedral of Our Lady of Hungary is the fourth largest church in the country.
        Its architecture is characterised by the mixture of Roman, gothic and eastern Byzantine
        style elements.</string>

    <string name="pantheon_description">The National Pantheon in Szeged sorrounds the Votive Church in
    Dóm Square. This square depicts the reliefs and statues of many famous hungarian poets, writers,
    scientists and politicians. It is a beautiful and breathtaking site for anyone to visit!</string>

    <string name="synagogue_description">The Synagogue, which was built 113 years ago,
        is a very famous destination for students, hungarian and foreigner groups. It’s open every day
        (except Saturdays and Jewish holidays) for tourists and for groups. Guided tours are also
        available in English for foreigner groups.</string>

    <string name="arkad_description">Situated in the heart of the city, the Árkád is Szeged\'s most
    prominent shopping malls. With over 130 shops it is the biggest shopping mall of the region. Its
    lovely and modern design and happy atmosphere, its stylish coffeshops - the only Strarbucks in
    the region - will keep anyone entertained for a day!</string>

    <string name="napfenypark_description">Napfénypark is the biggest in territory shopping mall of Szeged.
    With over 35 stores and several restaurants and a big TESCO one can find everything they may need to get
    by in the city.</string>

    <string name="nagyaruhaz_description">Right in the center of the city and near every University
    building Nagyáruház is one of Szeged\'s most lively places. It has several fresh restaurants, a
    COOP shop and several other useful shops. </string>

    <string name="plaza_description">Szeged Plaza is Szeged\'s entertainment center for those who
    look for the following: cinema and gokarting. It has more than 30 shops waiting for visitors and
    a beautiful view with the mall facing a wonderful lake. A true joy for those looking for calm shopping!</string>


</resources>